hugoboss.com 2017-06-23

# Privacy Statement

## Hugo Boss Privacy Policy

## Last Updated February 2016

## Effective March 1, 2016

We at Hugo Boss USA are committed to protecting the information that you share with us, and explaining how we collect, process, and share that information online.

## What information does this Privacy Policy cover?

This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information collected in the United States on: websites, mobile applications or in controlled widgets embedded in communication platforms with a link to this Privacy Policy (“Sites”). It also applies to Personal Information collected at freestanding Retail and Outlet stores operated by Hugo Boss Retail, Inc. It does not apply to any other information collected by HUGO BOSS Fashions, Inc. or Hugo Boss Retail, Inc. or its other United States based affiliates (“Hugo Boss USA”) through any other means. By “Personal Information,” we mean information that identifies you personally. It covers how we collect, use, and share that Personal Information as of the date that this Privacy Policy is posted. This Policy also doesn’t apply to any Sites maintained or operated by other companies, by any affiliates or subsidiaries or partners of Hugo Boss USA or otherwise linked to our Sites.

## You Consent to Transfer Your Personal Information to the United States

Hugo Boss USA is headquartered in the United States. If you decide to use this Site, your Personal Information may be transferred to the United States, and processed according to the terms described in this Privacy Policy. The laws in the United States may not be considered adequate by authorities in your home country. If you prefer not to have your Personal Information transferred to the United States, don’t use this Site. Otherwise, by using this Site, you expressly consent and authorize Hugo Boss to transfer your Personal Information to destinations outside your home country, and process it according to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## What types of Personal Information do we collect about our online visitors?

We receive and store certain types of information from you whenever you interact with our Sites to deliver the products you request from us, and help improve your overall shopping experience. For example, like many other websites, we drop “cookies” and store other web-based files on user devices to get certain types of information when your web browser accesses our Site.

**Information You Provide.** We generally collect only Personal Information you voluntarily provide to us. We don't require you to give us Personal Information to access certain public areas of our Site. This is true unless you live in a country that defines Personal Information to include network identifiers like your Internet Protocol addresses. For some secure areas of our Site, however, we require you to provide Personal Information when you use specific features. For example, we collect Personal Information from you when you: 

  1. Ask to register with us online or at a Hugo Boss Retail Store1
  2. Sign up for our newsletter2
  3. Request we alert you when an item or type of item is back in stock
  4. Participate in promotions or surveys
  5. Submit comments, reviews, or other user-generated content
  6. Connect or interact with us through social networks (e.g., Facebook, Google+, Twitter) or Live Chat
  7. Request customer or technical support3

This Personal Information, for example, may include your: 

  1. Name
  2. Postal or billing address
  3. Geolocation (depending on the settings of your mobile device)
  4. E-mail address
  5. Social Media account information (username and website)
  6. Telephone or mobile number
  7. Payment card information

If you can’t or choose not to provide us with the Personal Information we reasonably require, we may be unable to provide you with the information or services you have requested.

**Information Collected Through Technology.** We also obtain information in other ways through technology. Some of this information may be linked to you personally. This information helps our Sites function correctly and supports the work we do to understand the needs of our customers. Here are some examples.

**Device Information.** Depending on the permissions you’ve granted and other factors, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device when you download or use apps created by our Sites, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, certain player search results, and other personalized content. Examples of the device information we may collect includes: 

  * Attributes such as the operating system, hardware version, device settings, file and software names and types, battery and signal strength, and device identifiers.
  * Device locations, including specific geographic locations, such as through GPS, Bluetooth, or WiFi signals.
  * Connection information such as the name of your mobile operator or ISP, browser type, language and time zone, mobile phone number and IP address.

Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services, and we encourage you to contact your device manufacturer for detailed instructions on how to do that. 

**Payment Information.** If you purchase a product on our Site, we will collect payment card information from you, including your name, expiration date, authentication code, and billing address. We will securely transmit this information consistent with payment card industry rules to the appropriate payment facilitators. We may offer you the option to save information about the method and choice of payment on our Site. If you save this payment card information on our Site, you will be able to add, delete, or modify that information at any time using your account settings.

## Do we advertise online?

We advertise in a number of ways, including online through managed social media presences, and on other unaffiliated sites and mobile applications. To understand how our advertising campaigns are performing, we may collect certain information via our Sites through our advertising service providers. We or our vendors use several common online tracking tools to collect this information, such as browser and flash cookies, web beacons and other, similar technologies. The information we collect includes IP addresses, the number of page visits, pages viewed via our Sites, search engine referrals, browsing activities over time and across other websites following your visit to one of our Sites or applications, and responses to advertisements and promotions on the websites and applications where we advertise. We also use certain information to: 

  * Present tailored ads, including banner ads and splash ads that appear as you log-in or off of your online accounts via our Sites;
  * Identify new visitors to our Sites;
  * Recognize returning visitors;
  * Advertise on other websites and mobile applications not affiliated with us;
  * Analyze the effectiveness of our advertisements; 
  * Better understand our audience, customers, or other Site visitors; and
  * Determine whether you might be interested in new products or services.

**Controlling Our Tracking Tools.** Our browser may give you the ability to control cookies. How you do so, however, depends on your browser and the type of cookie. Certain browsers can be set to reject all browser cookies. If you configure your computer to block all cookies, you may disrupt certain web page features and limit the functionality we can provide when you visit or use our Sites. If you block or delete cookies, not all of the tracking that we have described in this policy will stop. Some browsers have a “ **Do Not Track** ” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These browser features are still not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals.

**Controlling Online Interest-Based Ads.** We sometimes work with online advertising vendors to provide you with relevant and useful ads. This may include ads served on or through our Sites. This may also include ads served on other companies’ websites. These ads may be based on information collected by us or third parties. For example, your postal code may be used to target an ad for people in your area. These ads may also be based on your activities on our Sites or on third party websites. For more information about our ad service provider and its cookies, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, you may visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. In addition, users may prevent Google’s collection of data generated by your use of the Sites (including your IP address) by downloading and installing a Browser Plugin available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>. 

## How we use and share your Personal Information?

We disclose Personal Information to external entities to perform support services for us and they may access your Personal Information for the purposes of performing those support services. We may also share what we know about you with unaffiliated third parties for our own or their own marketing purposes, or offer you the products and services of affiliated or unaffiliated third parties. To the extent legally permitted, we may combine your online information with information collected from offline sources or information we already have. We may also use and disclose certain Personal Information to our corporate affiliates as well as others for any purpose allowed by law.

**Hugo Boss Business Activities.** We process and may disclose your Personal Information to others to:

  * Respond to your questions, complaints, or reviews of our product or services;
  * Administer contests, promotions, or surveys;
  * Send you communications, including ads, electronic newsletters, or other offers or opportunities tailored to you;
  * Enable our advertisers to provide you with more personalized content, and track the effectiveness of certain advertising campaigns;
  * Comply with applicable law, obey judicial orders, cooperate with law enforcement authorities, or prevent any suspected illegal activities; 
  * Help us run our business; or
  * For any other everyday business purposes, such as product development and Site administration.

**Authorized Service Providers.** We use other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Those functions include payment card processors, shipping vendors, third party logistic providers, call-center support, e commerce service providers, analyzing or hosting data on cloud-based servers, and other companies that help us provide and improve our products and services. We may disclose your Personal Information to these companies and other individuals performing services in the United States or other locations where Hugo Boss maintains a facility.

**Sale of the Businesses.** If we sell all or part of our business, Personal Information may be transferred to the purchaser in connection with that transaction. We will use reasonable efforts to include contractual provisions that require the purchaser to treat your Personal Information consistent with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**Other Disclosures.** We may otherwise disclose Personal Information as permitted or required by law, when we believe in good faith it is necessary for safety purposes, required for legal reporting, or to protect our legal rights or enforce our Terms of Use or any applicable rules, or to protect the rights of others. We may also disclose Personal Information to our auditors, legal advisors, or to respond to a subpoena or other law enforcement request. We may also aggregate information that we gather about you (e.g., online sales, traffic patterns) and provide these statistics to others in aggregate form. 

## What choices do you have about the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information?

If you signed up to receive newsletters or other marketing communications from us, you can opt-out any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the message. You can also log-in to your account to opt-out and update your marketing preferences at any time. Even after you opt-out or update your marketing preferences, please allow sufficient time to process your marketing preferences. It may take up to **10 days** to process your e-mail related requests, and up to 30 days for all other marketing-related requests. And even after you’ve opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us, we may still contact you for transactional or informational purposes. These include, for example, customer service issues, returns or product-related inquiries, surveys or recalls, or any questions regarding a specific order.

## What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard your Personal Information?

The security and confidentiality of your Personal Information matters to us. That’s why we have technical, administrative, and physical controls in place to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. For example, we encrypt payment card information you submit to us using Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) technology that helps protect information during transport to our Site. Of course, we transmit the entire payment card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing in accordance with payment card rules. We also review our security procedures periodically to consider appropriate new technology and updated methods. Even so, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measure is ever perfect or impenetrable.

## How can you access, update, or block your Personal Information?

You can update the Personal Information you provided to us by logging-in to your profile, and making the appropriate changes or corrections yourself. You can also contact us directly any time at the address below to update your Personal Information. If you wish to de-activate your account, you may do so by contacting our customer support team at customerservice-us@hugoboss.com Once you do so, your account will then be de-activated on a going-forward basis, although certain personal information may still be retained in accordance with our Record Retention Policy or to the extent necessary to comply with applicable law.

You can opt-out of receiving HUGO BOSS marketing e-mails at any time by emailing your unsubscribe request to [customerservice-us@hugoboss.com.](mailto:customerservice-us@hugoboss.com)

## Minors and Children Under 13

Our Sites are not intended for minors. We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 or knowingly track the use of our Sites by minors.

## How can you file a complaint, ask questions, or send us comments about this Privacy Policy?

If you have any questions, have a complaint, or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, e-mail us at [customerservice-us@hugoboss.com.](mailto:customerservice-us@hugoboss.com) or call or write to us. We will investigate your complaint, and use reasonable efforts to respond to you as soon as possible. 

Our postal address is:

Hugo Boss Fashions, Inc.

Attn.: Privacy Office

55 Water Street, 48th Floor

New York, NY 10041

**For California Residents.** California Civil Code (section 1798.83) gives Hugo Boss customers who are California residents the right to request certain information about our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. If you wish to make this type of request, please e-mail, or write to us at the address provided above.

## How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material change to this privacy policy in regard to how we collect, use, disclose, or otherwise process Personal Information, we will prominently post the updated Privacy Policy. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective 10 days after our posting the updated Privacy Policy. Where required to do so by law, we may seek your prior consent to any material changes we make to this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with our Privacy Policy changes, you may de-activate your account., or opt out.

* * *

1 <https://www.hugoboss.com/us/account?dwcont=C193708365>  
2 [http://www.hugoboss.com/us/newsletter?email&utm_source=site&utm_medium=site&utm_campaign=email](http://www.hugoboss.com/us/newsletter?email&utm_source=site&utm_medium=site&utm_campaign=email)  
3 <https://www.hugoboss.com/us/contactus#contactanker>
